[{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":28,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat böjzöl. Én is sokat...","target_words":["böjzök","böjzöm"],"esp_response":"böjzök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":25,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat bölszöl. Én is sokat...","target_words":["bölszök","bölszöm"],"esp_response":"bölszök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":42,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat brágaklasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["brágaklok","brágaklom"],"esp_response":"brágaklom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":15,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat brüjlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["brüjlök","brüjlöm"],"esp_response":"brüjlök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":11,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat büglesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["büglök","büglöm"],"esp_response":"büglök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":16,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat csíszlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["csíszlok","csíszlom"],"esp_response":"csíszlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":48,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat driládzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["driládzok","driládzom"],"esp_response":"driládzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":44,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat drubódzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["drubódzok","drubódzom"],"esp_response":"drubódzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":3,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat femlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["femlek","femlem"],"esp_response":"femlek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":4,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat feténylesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["feténylek","feténylem"],"esp_response":"feténylek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":2,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat fibamlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["fibamlok","fibamlom"],"esp_response":"fibamlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":9,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat flagánylasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["flagánylok","flagánylom"],"esp_response":"flagánylok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":39,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat flagárzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["flagárzok","flagárzom"],"esp_response":"flagárzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":26,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat flűröklesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["flűröklök","flűröklöm"],"esp_response":"flűröklök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":17,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat flüröslesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["flüröslök","flüröslöm"],"esp_response":"flüröslök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":33,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat fretszel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["fretszek","fretszem"],"esp_response":"fretszek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":40,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat frilegszel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["frilegszek","frilegszem"],"esp_response":"frilegszem"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":50,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat herégszel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["herégszek","herégszem"],"esp_response":"herégszem"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":30,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat hilarzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["hilarzok","hilarzom"],"esp_response":"hilarzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":10,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat jüslesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["jüslök","jüslöm"],"esp_response":"jüslök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":22,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat juszlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["juszlok","juszlom"],"esp_response":"juszlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":23,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat klibamlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["klibamlok","klibamlom"],"esp_response":"klibamlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":19,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat klörlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["klörlök","klörlöm"],"esp_response":"klörlök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":37,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat lorjódzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["lorjódzok","lorjódzom"],"esp_response":"lorjódzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":36,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat málapszol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["málapszok","málapszom"],"esp_response":"málapszok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":14,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat marzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["marzok","marzom"],"esp_response":"marzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":34,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat narjárzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["narjárzok","narjárzom"],"esp_response":"narjárzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":20,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat nyáslasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["nyáslok","nyáslom"],"esp_response":"nyáslok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":21,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat pebzel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["pebzek","pebzem"],"esp_response":"pebzek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":47,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat piragszol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["piragszok","piragszom"],"esp_response":"piragszom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":53,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat pivegszel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["pivegszek","pivegszem"],"esp_response":"pivegszem"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":7,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat pratánylasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["pratánylok","pratánylom"],"esp_response":"pratánylok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":43,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat prilegzel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["prilegzek","prilegzem"],"esp_response":"prilegzem"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":12,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat prűrlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["prűrlök","prűrlöm"],"esp_response":"prűrlök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":38,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat ribegzel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["ribegzek","ribegzem"],"esp_response":"ribegzek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":49,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat ribzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["ribzok","ribzom"],"esp_response":"ribzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":13,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat ruslasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["ruslok","ruslom"],"esp_response":"ruslok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":45,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat siladzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["siladzok","siladzom"],"esp_response":"siladzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":46,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat sojzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["sojzok","sojzom"],"esp_response":"sojzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":35,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat spatárzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["spatárzok","spatárzom"],"esp_response":"spatárzok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":8,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat spéslesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["spéslek","spéslem"],"esp_response":"spéslek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":31,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat spibaklasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["spibaklok","spibaklom"],"esp_response":"spibaklok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":54,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat spilágzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["spilágzok","spilágzom"],"esp_response":"spilágzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":51,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat sprogzol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["sprogzok","sprogzom"],"esp_response":"sprogzom"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":41,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat sprökszöl. Én is sokat...","target_words":["sprökszök","sprökszöm"],"esp_response":"sprökszöm"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":5,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat spűmlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["spűmlök","spűmlöm"],"esp_response":"spűmlök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":29,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat sűzlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["sűzlök","sűzlöm"],"esp_response":"sűzlök"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":18,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat szirlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["szirlok","szirlom"],"esp_response":"szirlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":6,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat sztremlesz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["sztremlek","sztremlem"],"esp_response":"sztremlek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":24,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat tínylasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["tínylok","tínylom"],"esp_response":"tínylok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":32,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat tiregzel. Én is sokat...","target_words":["tiregzek","tiregzem"],"esp_response":"tiregzek"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":1,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat tomlasz. Én is sokat...","target_words":["tomlok","tomlom"],"esp_response":"tomlok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":27,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat trilszol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["trilszok","trilszom"],"esp_response":"trilszok"},{"file_name":"lakok_1_high_typical","list_number":1,"word_rank":52,"prompt":"Te bizony sokat vilakszol. Én is sokat...","target_words":["vilakszok","vilakszom"],"esp_response":"vilakszom"}]
